I'm somebody who is now going through a transformative process.
I'm starting to feel more like myself than I ever have in my life.
And I think it's largely in part because I am creating boundaries and space
for me to live how I want to live and not have to react to things
and do things in the protective way that I've been taught to live.
And I taught myself to live like that
because I didn't want to push people away by being too much.
I didn't want people to feel like I wasn't worth their friendship.
By being too much.
I didn't want people to judge me by being too much.
And so I made adjustments.
And those adjustments were to my detriment
because I wasn't getting fed the way that I really needed to be.
It feels like these are sacrifices that we make
just to be a part of civilization or society.
But it starts to hurt you as you get older
because it feels like you are not getting those nutrients that you needed.